Guide to the National Forum on Life Cycles and Volunteering records,1996-1998.
National Forum on Life Cycles and Volunteering records,1996-1998.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
National Forum on Life Cycles and Volunteering records, 1996-1998.
23-25-2977
New York State College of Human Ecology.National Forum on Life Cycles and Volunteering.
1.6 cubic ft.
Published materials, correspondence, newspaper articles, surveys, video.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, meeting minutes, advertising, alumni surveys, a video "The Impact on Work, Family and Mid-life Issues," information on speakers, and other records of a New York State College of Human Ecology conference held April 30 - May 1, 1998.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, meeting minutes, advertising, a video "The Impact on Work, Family and Mid-life Issues", information on speakers, and other records of a New York State College of Human Ecology conference held April 30 - May 1, 1998.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology.; New York State College of Human Ecology--Conferences.
Subjects:
Volunteerism--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Contents
  - Beginnings: The Arrival of Margaret Hendricks, Formulation of a Topic, and Initial Goals and Plans, October 1996-October 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Steering Committee: The Selection Process, Profiles of Candidates, Offer and Acceptance Letters, and Final List, February 1997-July 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Steering Committee: Agendas, Minutes and Notes, February 1997-July 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with New York Congressman Amory Houghton and New York Office of National and Community Service Executive Director Nikki Smith, January 1997-July 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Resources: Academic and Research Materials on Volunteerism Consulted by Hendricks, Fall 1996-July 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Budgets, Contracts, and Travel, March 1997 - April 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Expenses and Deposits, April 1997-April 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Marketing and Advertisement, April 1997-April 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - America's Promise and the President's Summit in Washington, DC, April 27, 1997 - January-May, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Published Materials on Cornell, the National Forum, and the President's Summit (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Articles, Newsletters and Magazines on Volunteerism, September 1975-February 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Speakers Part 1 - Correspondence and Profiles: Donna S. Anderson, S. Jeffrey Bastable, Syrelle Bernstein, Paula J. Beugen, Bonnie T. Brannon, Jeffrey L. Brudney, Christine G. Franklin, Vicki Clark, Susan J. Ellis, Robert K. Goodwin, and Donald N. Johnson (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Speakers Part II - Ronald Kinnamon, Edward J. Kramer, Nancy Latimer, Marjorie Ohaus Lillard, Miriam Lyons-Frolow, Charles P. Mazza, Marsha D. McCormick, Dagmar E. McGill, Phyllis Moen, Jean M. O'Neil, Anne Firor Scott, Kenneth R. Smith, Gretchen E. Stringer, Jean Szabadi, and Mary Wolf (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Speakers Part III - Introducers' Letters, Accommodations, and Honoraria, and Speaker Information, Feb. 9, 1998 - Apr. 27, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Videoconference: Plans, Program, Notes and Speakers, July 1997-May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Confirmation Letters to Videoconference Sponsors (Red Cross and VA Tech), March-April 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with Volunteer Organizations and Sponsors: The Association of Junior Leagues International, America's Promise, The Partnership, The Points of Light Foundation, Sisters of America, Cooperative Extension, YMCA, YWCA, PCCW, C&PL, HOBY, Winter 1994-April 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - College of Human Ecology Advancement Committee: Correspondence, Agendas and Minutes, September 1996-May 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Human Ecology Alumni Association (HEAA) Profiles, Correspondence, and Meetings, February 1997-July 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Awards for Outstanding Volunteer Work in Conjunction with the National Forum: Alumni Survey and Award Applications; Award Letters; Information and Correspondence with Martha Ohaus, June 1997-March 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Final Drafts: Schedule, Program, Speakers, and Information Packets; Bibliography, April-May 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Forum, Program and Session Evaluation Samples; Response Cards and Follow-Up Letters (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Surveys (A-Z), 1998 (Box 3)
  - The Impact on Work, Family and Mid-Life Issues, 1998-05-01; V-539
    two copies